teapartypatriots.org 2014-11-02

# Privacy | Tea Party Patriots

**Introduction**

**Tea Party Patriots, Inc** (the “Company”) publishes the website **www.teapartypatriots.org** (the “Site”).  The Company is the owner of that Site.   The Company seeks to respect your privacy.  This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect during your use of the Site.

To be eligible to use the Site, you must meet the following criteria and represent and warrant that you: (1) are 18 years of age or older; (2) are not currently restricted from the Site; (3) have full power and authority to enter into this Agreement and doing so will not violate any other agreement to which you are a party; and (4) will not violate any rights of the Company, including intellectual property rights such as copyright or trademark rights.

**Collected Information Provided by User**

The Site may require certain personal information in order to operate as designed.  Requested information for use of the Site may include your telephone number, e-mail address, postal address, and name and other identifying information.

**Additional Collected Information**

The Company will also collect non-personally identifiable information. This will typically include browser type, language preference, IP address, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.  The Company collects this data to optimize and iterate to best serve its users. This information will never be released on an individual basis, but may be released in a compiled manner.

The Company may also use cookies or web beacons to track a user’s interactions with the Site. This information will be used for internal purposes only to optimize the Site.  Users can opt-out of cookies by utilizing the settings provided in their browsers.

**Use of Collected Information**

The Company believes that the privacy of its users is paramount and strives to use their data only in ways outlined in this Privacy Policy. Most uses of data are for internal purposes only. The Company may also use data to provide you with goods or services you request using the Site.  The Company may occasionally inform users of new releases and features via any communication methods you have provided to the Site.

**Third Parties:**   The Company may engage certain Site providers for additional features (i.e. hosting, commerce, etc.).  The Company will thoroughly examine the privacy policies of partners to ensure that its users’ data is safe and taken care of responsibly. Third parties will not be able to use information in ways that are prohibited by this Privacy Policy.

**Advertising:**   The Company may partner with advertising partners to provide users with targeted and useful contextual advertisements. These partners may set cookies which enable them to recognize your computer and compile information about you or others who use your computer. Ad networks often use this information to better target advertisements that they think will be of use to you.  This Privacy Policy solely governs the use of information and cookies set by the Site and not by any third-party advertising partners.

**Transfers:**   The Company may share data internally with its affiliate companies and may disclose certain information in the event that it is merged, acquired, sold, or some of its assets are acquired. If, in the Company’s discretion, your information will be handled in a materially different manner than it was by the Company, you may have the opportunity to opt-out of having your information shared with any acquirer.

**Law Enforcement:**   The Company will cooperate with law enforcement and disclose any requested information if the Company believes, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to: (i) handle fraud, attacks against our systems, or security conflicts, (ii) remain compliant with currently applicable state and federal laws or regulations, (iii) continue to abide by our Terms of Use, or (iv) protect the public or the Company from any attacks against intellectual or physical property rights.

**Your Responsibility Online**

You are responsible for all activity occurring under your accounts and shall comply with all applicable local, state, national, and foreign, laws, treaties and regulations in connection with your use of the Site, including those related to data privacy and the transmission of technical or personal data.  The Company cannot guarantee your safety and security and you should be aware that submitting any information and using the Site is done at your own risk.

**Managing Your Privacy**

Users can manage their privacy on the Company web site and can contact [support.teapartypatriots.org](http://support.teapartypatriots.org/) for further assistance and questions regarding this Privacy Policy.

**Jurisdiction**

All information passed through the Site is primarily handled in the United States but may from time to time be handled in any country in which the Company or its affiliate companies maintain facilities. By using the Site, you agree that the handling of your personal information and any communication through the Site will be governed by the laws of the United States and any applicable state laws.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, the Company may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in the Company’s sole discretion.  The Company encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Updated:  February 13, 2014.
